Welcome into Jaguars draft day number
two as we're getting ready to know some
of the newest Jaguars players and now
we're going to meet Emmanuel Pregnan
offensive lineman out of Oregon. First
of all, congratulations. Did you know
you're going to Jacksonville or just
excited to see whoever was going to
call?
Yeah, I mean
I didn't know I was going originally. I
was just waiting for my opportunity
honestly.
What has this experience been like?
Obviously getting to hear your name
called I'm sure was amazing but just
going through this process and getting
ready to go to the NFL. Oh man, it's
been a roller coaster in all honesty you
know.
Um
It's been a roller coaster and
it's just been a flurry of emotions and
I'm just excited. I'm I'm forever
grateful that that that I got this
opportunity and I'm ready to capitalize
in
any way I can.
A long successful career at Oregon, what
do you feel like uh prepared you the
most for the NFL?
I would say the culture, the environment
that is you know constantly
uh upheld at Oregon and and pushed upon
when it comes to that standard. I feel
like that environment just prepared me
to be a pro's pro and that's what I
believe I am now.
Going to be uh protecting Trevor
Lawrence, quarterback. What's your kind
of mindset when it comes to protecting
the QB?
My mindset is
I'll die for my quarterback. Nobody's
going to touch him with a 10-ft pole.
I'll give him all the time he needs. If
he wants to sit on the toilet, he's
going to sit on that toilet.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll let him know you said that. I'm
sure he'll be very happy to hear.
>> [laughter]
>> What are Jaguars players What are
Jaguars fans going to see when you take
the field in the fall?
They're going to see
a person with the absolute dog mentality
that's relentless
that's
durable, has a high IQ and is ready to
do whatever the team needs in order to
win.
Absolutely Emmanuel, welcome to Duval.
We'll see you in Jacksonville soon.
Thank you. Thank you for having me.